{"keywords": ["water", "has property", "spicy"], "sentence": "water isn't spicy.", "general_sentence": "water isn't usually spicy.", "question": "is water spicy?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "water is tasteless.", "cot_logic": "If something is spicy, then it must have the taste of spices. Water has no taste.", "generic": "water is spicy.", "general_question": "is water usually spicy?"}
{"keywords": ["shields", "made of", "grass"], "sentence": "shields are not made of grass.", "general_sentence": "shields are not generally made of grass.", "question": "are shields made of grass?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "shields are used for protection.", "cot_logic": "If something is made of grass, then it must be soft. Shields are not soft.", "generic": "shields are made of grass.", "general_question": "are shields usually made of grass?"}
{"keywords": ["penguins", "is a", "mammal"], "sentence": "penguins are not mammals.", "general_sentence": "penguins are not mammals.", "question": "are penguins a kind of mammal?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "penguins are birds.", "cot_logic": "If an animal is a mammal, then it has mammary glands that in female. Penguins do not produce milk.", "generic": "penguins are mammal.", "general_question": "are penguins mammal?"}
{"keywords": ["salmon", "capable of", "talk"], "sentence": "salmon cannot talk.", "general_sentence": "generally speaking, salmon cannot talk.", "question": "can salmon talk?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "salmon is a kind of fish.", "cot_logic": "If salmon can talk, they can produce sounds with their vocal cords. Salmon do not have vocal cords.", "generic": "salmon can talk.", "general_question": "can salmon usually talk?"}
{"keywords": ["shoes", "has a", "sleeves"], "sentence": "shoes have no sleeve.", "general_sentence": "most shoes have no sleeve.", "question": "do shoes have sleeves?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "shoe is a type of footwear.", "cot_logic": "Sleeves are parts of garments that cover the arms. Shoes are not garments.", "generic": "shoes have sleeves.", "general_question": "do shoes usually have sleeves?"}
{"keywords": ["kitchen", "has a", "books"], "sentence": "books are not parts of a kitchen.", "general_sentence": "books are usually not parts of a kitchen.", "question": "does a kitchen have books?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "kitchen is used for cooking.", "cot_logic": "Books are typically found in rooms that are used for reading or studying. Kitchens are not used for reading or studying.", "generic": "kitchen has books.", "general_question": "does a kitchen usually have books?"}
{"keywords": ["cigarettes", "made of", "firelighters"], "sentence": "cigarettes are not made of firelighters.", "general_sentence": "cigarettes are not made of firelighters.", "question": "are cigarettes made of firelighters?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "cigarettes are used for smoking.", "cot_logic": "Firelighters are materials that are used to start fires. Cigarettes are not used to start fires.", "generic": "cigarettes are made of firelighters.", "general_question": "are cigarettes generally made of firelighters?"}
{"keywords": ["bananas", "is a", "tree"], "sentence": "bananas are not trees.", "general_sentence": "bananas are not trees.", "question": "are bananas a kind of trees?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "bananas are a type of fruit.", "cot_logic": "If something is a tree, then it has an elongated trunk. Bananas do not have elongated trunks.", "generic": "bananas are trees.", "general_question": "are bananas trees?"}
{"keywords": ["elephant", "capable of", "jump"], "sentence": "elephants cannot jump.", "general_sentence": "usually, elephants cannot jump.", "question": "can elephants jump?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "elephants can walk slowly.", "cot_logic": "Jumping needs sufficient force to overcome the effects of gravity. Elephants are too heavy to overcome gravity.", "generic": "elephants can jump.", "general_question": "can most elephants jump?"}
{"keywords": ["computer", "is a", "intelligent being"], "sentence": "computers aren't intelligent beings.", "general_sentence": "computers aren't intelligent beings.", "question": "is a computer an intelligent being?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "computer is a type of electronic device.", "cot_logic": "Intelligent beings have the ability to think. Computers cannot think like humans do.", "generic": "computers are intelligent beings.", "general_question": "is computer usually an intelligent being?"}
{"keywords": ["standing", "causes", "feeling happy"], "sentence": "standing doesn't make one feel happy.", "general_sentence": "standing doesn't usually make one feel happy.", "question": "does standing cause someone to feel happy?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "standing is a kind of motion.", "cot_logic": "If something causes people to feel happy, then it must be entertaining. Standing is not entertaining.", "generic": "standing makes one feel happy.", "general_question": "does standing usually make one feel happy?"}
{"keywords": ["needles", "used for", "writing"], "sentence": "needles are not used for writing.", "general_sentence": "needles are not usually used for writing.", "question": "are needles used for writing?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "needles are used for sewing.", "cot_logic": "Writing implements are tools that are used to produce written words. Needles are not such tools for this purpose.", "generic": "needles are used for writing.", "general_question": "are needles usually used for writing?"}
{"keywords": ["lion", "desires", "eat grass"], "sentence": "lions don't want to eat grass.", "general_sentence": "lions don't usually want to eat grass.", "question": "do lions want to eat grass?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "lions eat meat.", "cot_logic": "Graminivores eat grass. Lion is not a graminivore.", "generic": "lions want to eat grass.", "general_question": "do lions usually want to eat grass?"}
{"keywords": ["bomb", "is a", "food"], "sentence": "bombs are not food.", "general_sentence": "bombs are not food.", "question": "are bombs edible?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "bombs are weapons.", "cot_logic": "Food is edible. Bombs are not edible.", "generic": "bomb is a food.", "general_question": "is bomb usually a food?"}
{"keywords": ["guns", "used for", "healing"], "sentence": "guns can't be used for healing.", "general_sentence": "generally, guns can't be used for healing.", "question": "are guns used for healing?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "guns are used for killing.", "cot_logic": "Healing instruments are tools that are used to treat injuries or illnesses. Guns are not tools that are used to treat injuries or illnesses.", "generic": "guns are used for healing.", "general_question": "are guns usually used for healing?"}
{"keywords": ["pets", "capable of", "divorce"], "sentence": "pets cannot divorce.", "general_sentence": "generally, pets cannot divorced.", "question": "can pets be divorced?", "answer": "no", "cot_fact": "pets are animals.", "cot_logic": "Divorce is the legal dissolution of a marriage. Pets do not have the legal capacity for marriages.", "generic": "pets can divorce.", "general_question": "can pets generally divorce?"}